(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
本日は鷹嶺ルイ 3Dお披露目配信にご来場いただき、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for joining us for the Takane Lui 3D debut stream today.
この配信は至って、そう、至って健全ですので...
This stream is very, yes, very wholesome, so...
...ご家族、お子様連れ、そして友達同士、いる方は恋人同士でお楽しみください。
...please enjoy it with your family, children, friends, or even your partner if you have one.
いない方は、そうですね、えー、一人でぶち上がっていきましょう。
For those who don't, well, let's just get hyped up alone!
盛り上がっていけるかー！？
Are you guys ready to get excited?!
うんうん、みんな盛り上がってるね。いい感じ。
Yeah, yeah, everyone's getting into it. Looking good.
ということで、開始までもうしばらくお待ちください。
With that said, please wait just a little longer until we start.
俺んとこ来ないか？
Won't you come to my place?
One Night Carnival
One Night Carnival 胸の奥
One Night Carnival, deep in my heart
ズキズキと音立ててる エンジェル
An angel making a throbbing sound
とにかくもう 学校や家には
Anyway, I don't want to go back to
帰りたくない
school or home anymore
※彼女はVTuberです。危険なので真似しないでください。
*She is a VTuber. It is dangerous, so please do not imitate her.
Angel...
A-hoo!
退屈に怯えてたのさ
I was scared of boredom
夜の闇に逃げ込んだ Angel
An angel who fled into the darkness of the night
俺たちまるで...
We are just like...
...捨て猫みたい
...stray cats
Angel!
Can you master baby! Master baby!
C'mon!
Yeah!
Can you master baby! Master baby!
Can you master baby! SORO!
瞬きもせずに
Without even blinking
俺たちは光の渦に巻き込まれてく
We're getting caught up in a vortex of light
雲の隙間に
In the gaps between the clouds
照らせ 蒼白き月を照らせ
Shine, illuminate the pale moon
星が瞬く Distance
The distance where the stars twinkle
寂しがり屋たちの伝説さ
It's the legend of the lonely ones
One Night Carnival fun-fun
A-hoo!
Hoo! Hoo!
風に香るタクティクスが
The tactics scenting the wind
俺の胸を締め付ける Angel
Are tightening my chest, Angel
今だけは... 今だけは...
Just for now... just for now...
哀しい歌 聞きたくないよ
I don't want to hear sad songs
Angel!
Can you master baby! Master baby!
Can you master baby! Be my baby!
Can you master baby! SORO! SORO!
俺たちが拒絶されたことに 理由なんてなかったよ
There was no reason why we were rejected
ただ 少しだけ不器用だったのかもしれない
Maybe we were just a little bit clumsy
恋しているのさ この夜に恋しているのさ
I'm in love, I'm in love with this night
やがて海が見える
Eventually the sea will be visible
寂しがり屋たちの伝説さ
It's the legend of the lonely ones
One Night Carnival fun-fun
あの頃の俺たち 闇の中じゃなきゃ夢見られなかった
The us back then, we couldn't dream unless it was in the darkness
あのミラーボールみたいに 明るくて まんまるなお月様に憧れただけさ
We just longed for that bright, round moon, like a mirror ball
行こうぜ ピリオドの向こうへ
Let's go beyond the period
まっすぐ海が見える
The sea is visible straight ahead
寂しがり屋たちの伝説さ
It's the legend of the lonely ones
One Night Carnival fun-fun
One Night Carnival O-Lo
Let's get to free!
Hoo! Hoo!
MIRA 作詞・作曲：Kanaria
MIRA Lyrics/Composition: Kanaria
ハイ回春捨てれない夢に戯れ 嫌い返して
Hi, rejuvenation, can't throw away dreams, playing, returning the hate
ハイ回春捨てれない君は誰 あれ 誰か愛して
Hi, rejuvenation, can't throw away, who are you? Oh, someone love me
ビビデビビデバット
Bibide-bibide-bat
抱きしめてラーラーラー
Embrace me, la la la
見せかけてラーラーラー
Pretend to, la la la
憧れは...
My yearning is...
あこがれてない
I'm not longing for it
慰めもない
There's no comfort either
血塗られた
Bloodstained
出てこないでら
Don't come out
怪しげなら
If it seems suspicious
あこがれてない
I'm not longing for it
慰めもない
There's no comfort either
消えかけたなら
If it's fading away
あなたのそばで
Right by your side
赤い糸 絡まりもつれて
The red thread, tangled and snarled
浅い心も ざわめらかして
Making even a shallow heart rustle
泣き絆 隠していくんだ
I'll keep hiding my crying bonds
存在 私は くだらぬ馬車馬
My existence, a worthless workhorse
Bibi-de-Bibi-de-ba-to
あざやかなら
If it's vivid
目障りなら
If it's an eyesore
無慈悲でもない
It's not even merciless
痛みなどない
There's no pain either
血塗られた
Bloodstained
出てこないでら
Don't come out
偽善者のら
If it's a hypocrite
情けはない
There's no mercy
情などない
There's no compassion
血塗られた
Bloodstained
あなたのそばで
Right by your side
はい、ということでみなさん、またかね〜！
Alright, everyone! Matakane~!
はい、ホロライブおんな…あ、ホロライブ、ホロライブ6期生、holoXの女幹部、
I'm the executive officer of holoX, Hololive's 6th generation,
鷹嶺ルイと申します。
Takane Lui!
ついに3Dになりましたー！
I'm finally in 3D!
どう、どう？私のスタイル。
How is it? My style.
全身で見てどうですか？
What do you think of the full-body view?
美しいでしょう？
Beautiful, isn't it?
ん〜ん〜ん〜。みんなもね、「美しい」って言ってくれてますね。よかった〜！
Hehe. Everyone's saying "beautiful" too. I'm so glad!
はい、ということで2曲ね、続けてお送りさせていただいたんですけれども。
Alright, so I just performed two songs in a row.
最初はみんなね、「これで来るんじゃないか？」って思ってたんじゃないですかね。
At first, everyone probably thought I'd start with this one,
ワンナイトカーニバル。
One Night Carnival.
こちらはね、もう気づいてる人もいたんですけど、
Some people already noticed,
holoXのみんなにコーラスをしてもらいました！気づいた？気づいたかな？
but I had all of holoX do the chorus! Did you notice? Did you?
はい、ということで初配信のリベンジを今日、させていただきました。
So, I got to have my revenge for the debut stream today.
全部ね、マネちゃんに怒られずに歌うことができました！ぱちぱちぱちぱちぱち！
I was able to sing everything without getting scolded by my manager! *Clap clap clap!*
ということで、あ、そういえば、こっちか。
And so... oh, by the way, it's over here.
ハッシュタグ #鷹嶺ルイ3D で、
Using the hashtag #TakaneLui3D,
先ほどの、ま、クソコラ感、クソコラ感満載の
those, well, meme-tastic...
「ワンナイトカーニバル」のお写真だったりとか、
...shitty collage photos from "One Night Carnival,"
ちょっとね、かっこいい「MIRA」の…
or the cool ones from "MIRA"...
MIRA、最終的にホークアイになったの、見ましたか？
Did you see how "MIRA" ended with the Hawkeye effect?
そういった写真を、どんどん #鷹嶺ルイ3D で呟いてくださると嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if you keep tweeting photos like those with #TakaneLui3D.
たくさん呟いて私をトレンド1位にしてください。よろしく！
Tweet a lot and help me reach #1 on trending! Thanks!
ということで、ホークアイ見たいって言ってる人がいたので、
Since some of you said you wanted to see Hawkeye,
ホークアイちょっとやってみるか。できるかな？
I'll try doing Hawkeye now. Can I do it?
う〜ん…ぱっ！
Hmm... Ta-da!
おお！そこにいる、チャンネル登録してない君。
Oh! You there, who hasn't subscribed yet.
チャンネル登録してないけどちょっと、3Dだし見てみようかなっていう、あなた！
You, who isn't subscribed but thought you'd check it out since it's 3D!
はい、今すぐチャンネル登録ポチッと押してください。はい、押すよね？
Go ahead and hit that subscribe button right now! You'll do it, right?
はい、ルイ・シュ・ブリタニアが命じてるよ。
Yes, Lui shu Britannia commands you!
ということでチャンネル登録みなさん、よろしくお願いします。
So, please subscribe, everyone!
はい、ということで、そういえば、このステージ、いかがですか？
Alright, and by the way, how do you like this stage?
ちょっと月明かりがね、すごく綺麗で、
The moonlight is just so beautiful.
あの、ちょっと「ワンナイトカーニバル」で「まんまるな お月様に」って言ってるけど、三日月っつってね。
Even though I said "perfectly round moon" in "One Night Carnival," it's actually a crescent moon.
まんまるじゃねーじゃん、つってね。これ気づいた人いるかな？
I'm like, "It's not round at all!" I wonder if anyone noticed that.
なんか、ちょっと任務の場所みたいじゃないですか？
It kind of looks like a location for a mission, doesn't it?
私、鷹嶺、ま、鷹なので、
Since I'm Takane, well, a hawk,
こういったね、森に結構…いたりとかするんですけど。
I'm often in forests like this.
holoXの任務とかもよくここで待ち合わせとかをするので、
We often meet up here for holoX missions,
こういったセットを作っていただきました！どうですか？
so I had this set made! What do you think?
めちゃくちゃおしゃれでしょう？
It's super stylish, isn't it?
あとね、なんかホロライブの先輩方にもぜひこのステージ使ってもらいたいなーということで、はい、このステージを作ってもらいました。
I also had this stage made so that my Hololive seniors could use it too!
おっしゃれ、おっしゃれ、おっしゃれ！
So stylish, so stylish, so stylish!
ということで、あ、そういえば、
So, oh, by the way,
私のお披露目は終わったんですけど、もう一匹お忘れじゃないですか？
my debut is over, but haven't you forgotten one more creature?
ね、つくねとつみれちゃんはお披露目ね、先にさせていただきましたが、
Tsukune and Sumire-chan already had their debuts earlier,
あいつのこと忘れてませんか？
but haven't you forgotten about that guy?
うーん、あ、みんなわかるかな？
Hmm, does everyone know who I'm talking about?
じゃあ、みんなで呼んでみましょうか。
Well, let's call him together.
あいつ寝てないかな、大丈夫かな。
I hope he's not asleep, I hope he's okay.
はい、ということで、ガンモー！
Alright, so... GANMO!
どこから来るんだ？
Where is he coming from?
おー、来た！飛んできた！
Oh, there he is! He's flying in!
や、ガンモめちゃくちゃ可愛いでしょ。
Isn't Ganmo just the cutest?
皆さんにご挨拶。はい、お願いします。
Say hello to everyone. Come on, please.
はい、ということで、私の腕に止まれるか？
Alright, now, can you land on my arm?
止まってみせてくれ。
Show us you can do it.
ガンモ、おっ、
Ganmo... Oh!
はぁー！いい子ですね。止まれた止まれた。
Ha! Good boy. You landed, you landed!
じゃあね、今夜は酒をあげよう。
Well then, I'll give you some sake tonight.
お酒飲んでよし。うん、いい子だ。
You're allowed to drink. Yeah, good boy.
あれ？ていうか、そもそもあの杖どこやったの？杖どこやってきた？
Wait, come to think of it, what happened to that staff? Where did you leave the staff?
杖、杖あんのかな？
Do I even have it?
なんかさ、私の今回のサムネに杖あったと思うんですけど、今ね、杖がないんですよ。
I think there was a staff in my thumbnail for this stream, but right now, I don't have it.
ちゃんと持って、あ！あれ？
Make sure you... Ah! What?
あー！どういう仕組みそれ？浮いてる。
Oh! How does that even work? It's floating!
あ、ちゃんと掴んで持ってきてくれたのね。ありがとう。
Oh, you were holding it and brought it to me. Thank you.
いや、ガンモめちゃ可愛い。
Man, Ganmo is so cute.
つくねとね、つみれもちゃんとセットでね。
Along with Tsukune and Sumire as a set.
ほら、見てください。この揺れ感。
Look at this swaying motion.
可愛いね。ちゃんと上目遣いしてますね、ガンモ。
So cute. He's doing the 'puppy-dog eyes' look, isn't he, Ganmo?
あえ？なに？あら？
Eh? What? Oh?
そういえば、『ワンナイト・カーニバル』の時出てこなかったもんね、君。
Come to think of it, you didn't show up during 'One Night Carnival', did you?
あ、じゃあちょっと私もサングラスつけさせてもらって...
Well, then let me put on some sunglasses too...
お、じゃあ一緒に写真でも撮る？こうかな？
Oh, shall we take a photo together? Like this?
はい、チーズ！
Say cheese!
あ、どう？どう？撮れた？
Oh, how is it? How is it? Did we get it?
はい。ということで、『ワンナイト・カーニバル』そして『ミラー』と歌わせていただきましたが、
Alright. So, I've sung 'One Night Carnival' and 'Mirror' so far,
この配信のサブテーマ、実はあるんですよ。
but there's actually a sub-theme for this stream.
タイトルにもあります、『鷹嶺ルイ 成長の軌跡』というね。
It's also in the title: 'Takane Lui's Growth Trajectory'.
ちょ、ちょっとこのサングラスつけて言うことじゃないんだけど。
Wait, this isn't something I should be saying while wearing these sunglasses.
ちょっとサングラス取るか。取って、よいしょ。
Let me take them off. Off they go, heave-ho.
はい、ということで。ちょっとエモいこと言うのに、あのサングラスだとね、私が笑っちゃうから。
Okay. I can't say anything emotional with those sunglasses on, I'd just end up laughing at myself.
ということで、サブテーマ『鷹嶺ルイの成長の軌跡』ということでね、
So, the sub-theme is 'Takane Lui's Growth Trajectory'.
私がデビューして半年ちょっと、半年少し以上活動してきましたが、
It's been a little over six months since my debut,
その成長の軌跡を皆さんと一緒にちょっと振り返っていきたいなっていうことと...
and I want to look back on that journey of growth with all of you...
あと私やっぱり歌が大好きで、歌を頑張っていきたいなっていう願いも込めて、
...and because I really love singing and want to keep working hard at it,
ちょっと歌中心のお披露目をさせていただければなと思います。
I've put together this debut showcase centered around songs.
なので最後まで楽しんでいってください。
So please enjoy it until the very end.
ちょっと水だけ飲んでもいいですか？
Can I just have some water?
水だけ飲みますね。ちょっと待ってください。
I'm going to drink some water. Please wait a moment.
はい。ということで、続いての曲行きましょうか。
Alright. Now, let's move on to the next song.
続いての曲は、皆さんも結構記憶に新しいんじゃないでしょうか。
This one is probably quite fresh in your memories.
この曲聴いてください。『プロローグ』。
Please listen to this song. 'Prologue'.
目蓋軽く 髪の毛と かき分けた指
Your eyelids light, your hair, and the fingers that brushed it aside
壊れそうで どこか寂しげな背中
That back of yours, looking fragile and somehow lonely
頼りない太陽を 滲ませながら
While blurring the unreliable sun
微笑んだその横顔 見つめていた
I was staring at your profile as you smiled
を招き そのすべて
invitations... all of it...
視界に入ってくるの
They come into my field of vision.
心が波打つ痛みに
The pain of my heart rippling...
どうして気づいてしまったの
Why did I end up noticing it?
あなたを探してる
I'm looking for you.
隠した瞳の奥で
Deep within my hidden eyes.
誰にも見えぬように
So that no one can see...
行き場もなくて 彷徨いながら
While wandering with nowhere to go.
あなたと見る世界は
The world I see with you...
いつでも綺麗だった
...was always beautiful.
空にはひとつだけ
In the sky, there's just one...
淡く光る 小さな星が残ってる
...faintly glowing little star remaining.
求めては突き放す 読めない心
A heart that seeks yet pushes away, one I cannot read.
見つめられるほどに 嘘がつけない
The more you look at me, the more I cannot lie.
力なく点滅する あの街灯を
That streetlamp flickering feebly...
見上げてたその横顔は優しかった
...the profile of your face as you looked up was kind.
破れそうに膨らんで
Swelling as if about to burst...
真赤に熟れた果実は
...the deep red, ripened fruit...
誰かの摘む手を待っている
...is waiting for someone's hand to pluck it.
ねぇ それは私だった
Hey, that was me.
あなたが溢れてく
You are overflowing...
押さえた胸の鼓動だけ
Only the suppressed beating of my chest...
隠せない始まりを
...this beginning I cannot hide...
月から月へ 手のひらに伝えてゆくよ
...I'll transmit it from moon to moon, into my palm.
風は冷たいのに
Even though the wind is cold...
染まった心は赤いままで
...my stained heart remains red.
あなたに触れたいと思ってしまった
I ended up wanting to touch you.
どうして二人出会えたの
Why did the two of us meet?
痛くて 苦しくて
It's painful, it's agonizing...
それなら見えぬように
If so, then so it can't be seen...
どこかへ飛んでゆけ
...fly away somewhere.
そう思うのに
Even though I think that...
あなたを探してる
I'm looking for you.
何度も名前を呼んで
Calling your name over and over.
空にはひとつだけ
In the sky, there's just one...
淡く光る 小さな星を浮かべて
...faintly glowing little star floating.
君に触れたとき
When I touched you...
キミソラキセキ 作詞・作曲: ryo
Miracle in Your Sky - Lyrics & Composition: ryo
高鳴る鼓動が聞こえた
I heard my heart beating fast.
初めて知ったの 思いは
I realized it for the first time, these feelings...
…は力になる歌
...a song that becomes strength.
星屑ちりばめた空に
In the sky studded with stardust,
君へ届けと願う私の歌
my song, wishing it reaches you.
聞こえますか
Can you hear it?
I love you forever 最後には言えずにいた
I love you forever, I couldn't say it at the end.
今更だけど伝えたい想いがある
It's late, but there's a feeling I want to convey.
I love you 何度も何度でも聞いてほしい
I love you, I want you to hear it again and again.
君を愛してるから
Because I love you.
守るものなんて何もないはずだったのに
I was supposed to have nothing to protect,
君の存在が私を臆病にさせた
but your existence made me a coward.
失くした気持ちが少しずつ戻り始めてきて
The feelings I lost are starting to return bit by bit,
怖いんだ
and it's scary.
二人ならきっと
If it's the two of us, surely...
I love you forever 最後には言えずにいた
I love you forever, I couldn't say it at the end.
勇気を出して伝えたい想いがある
I want to muster my courage and tell you my feelings.
I love you だから何度もキスをしよう
I love you, so let's kiss many times.
君を愛してるから
Because I love you.
サヨナラが教えてくれた
The goodbye taught me
二人巡り会えた それで奇跡
that the two of us meeting was a miracle.
なんだね きっと
It really was, I'm sure.
I love you forever 最後に君に
I love you forever, at the last, to you...
こうして二人肩寄せ合っていられるうちに
while we can still be close like this.
I love you 何度も何度でも伝わるまで
I love you, again and again, until it reaches you.
君を愛してる サヨナラまた会える
I love you, goodbye, we'll meet again.
こうして二人いつの日か また目を閉じれば思い出せるよ
Like this, the two of us, one day, if I close my eyes I'll remember.
I love you だからもう二度と振り向かない
I love you, so I won't look back ever again.
君だ そばにいるから
It's you, because I'm by your side.
君を愛してる
I love you.
大変申し訳ございません！
I am terribly sorry!
こちらはね、あの、弁償させていただきますんで！
I will, um, compensate for this!
申し訳ございません、怒らないでください！
I'm so sorry, please don't be mad!
本当に、本当にごめんなさい！
Really, I'm really sorry!
ああ、本当にごめんなさい！
Ah, I'm really sorry!
え？ 禁酒？
Eh? No alcohol?
え、禁酒はちょっと、あの、刑が重くないですかね？
Eh, isn't no alcohol, like, a bit of a heavy punishment?
ちょっとそこは...
A bit much...
酒なしじゃ生きていけないのよ！
I can't live without alcohol!
ちょっと頼みますお願いします！
Please, I beg of you!
許して許して！
Forgive me, forgive me!
愛して...
Love you...
痛！痛！やめろ、やめろ！
Ow! Ow! Stop it, stop it!
やめろ、やめろ、やめろ！
Stop it, stop it, stop it!
痛いよ...
It hurts...
許してよ...
Forgive me...
どうしよう...
What should I do...?
じゃーん！はい、もう一つのステージは...
Tada! Yes, the next stage is...
...このバーステージです！
...this bar stage!
いや、このバーステージめっちゃおシャンじゃない？
Doesn't this bar stage look super stylish?
おシャンでしょ？なんか私らしくて...
Stylish, right? It's very 'me.'
私のね、あのイメージカラーであるワインレッドを...
I had them create this bar based on my image color,
...基調としたバーを作っていただきました。
...wine red.
実はね、このバー...
Actually, this bar is...
...色んなね仕掛けというかステージに分かれてるんですよ。
...divided into various gimmicks, or rather, stages.
三つのステージに分かれてるので...
It's divided into three stages, so...
...今ね、こちら紹介したいと思います。
...I'd like to introduce them now.
まずは後ろに見えるのがバーですね。
First, what you see behind me is the bar counter.
まあバーステージだからバーあるんだけど。
Well, it's a bar stage, so of course there's a bar.
バーね、はい。
The bar, yes.
結構ね、こちらでお酒を飲んだりとか...
You can drink here and such...
...まあHoloXが経営しているバーなので...
...well, it's managed by HoloX,
...ちょっとお会計はね、どのくらいになるか...
...so I can't guarantee how much...
...ちょっと保証はできませんけれども...
...the bill will be...
...皆さんでね、ぜひぜひお酒を飲みに来ていただければなと思います。
...but I hope everyone will come and have a drink.
はい。
Yes.
そして、こちら真ん中のステージは...
And then, this center stage is...
...椅子だったりね、ソファだったりがあるお洒落な...
...a stylish space with chairs and sofas,
...まあ観客席というかお酒を飲むスペースになってます。
...like an audience area for drinking.
で、このスペースめっちゃすごいんだけど見えるかな？
This space is actually amazing, can you see it?
こっちかな？こっち行くと...
Over here? If we go this way...
ジャジャーン！絵画が飾られてあるんですね。
Tada! There are paintings on the wall.
いやこれ凄くない？
Isn't this great?
いいね、おめでとうお洒落。
Nice, congrats on the style.
お洒落でしょ？
Stylish, right?
これね、椅子をどけたりとかテーブルをどけて...
I thought it would look cool to move the chairs
...あのこのねバックで踊ったりとかしてみたら...
...and tables and dance with this background.
...カッコいいんじゃないかなと思って。
I thought it would be cool.
ちょっとあの、ホロライブでやっぱり先輩方だったりとかね...
I thought this background would suit my Hololive senpais
...あと同期の皆だったりとか...
...and genmates
...今後ライブする時にダンスをさ、わーってやる時に...
...when they do high-energy dances in future lives.
...この背景合うんじゃないかなと思って。
This background would be perfect for that.
もうホロリスだから、ホロメンに使ってもらいたいがために...
Being a Hololive fan myself, I had this stage made so
...このねステージを作らせていただきました。
...the Holo-members can use it.
いやカッコいいでしょこれ。いやめっちゃカッコいい。
It's cool, isn't it? Super cool.
落ち着くね、アンティーク調のクロアになっているんですが。
It's a relaxing antique-style floor.
そしてそれだけじゃないんです。
And that's not all.
ラストの一つ。
One last one.
ドドドドドドド...
(Drumroll vocalization)
あーどうですかこれ！
How's this!
そう、バーのバーステージといえばやっぱりねライブステージ。
Yes, a bar stage needs a live performance stage.
そうジャズなねライブをしたりだったりとか...
I thought it would be stylish to have jazz lives
...オーケストラのライブをしたりだったりとかすると...
...or orchestral lives here...
...お洒落なんじゃないかなっていうことで...
...so I had this bar stage made...
...このバーステージ三... まあ三パターンの楽しみ方がありますよ...
...with three ways to enjoy it.
...ということで作らせていただきました。
That's why I had it made.
どうみんな？
What do you think?
ちょっとみんなのコメントが見たいからじゃあちょっと定位置に戻って...
I want to see your comments, so I'll return to the center...
大丈夫かな？はい。
Is this okay? Good.
どうですかね？皆さん気に入っていただけた？
Well? Did you all like it?
凄いお洒落。いいね。
Very stylish. Nice.
絵のところ2D写せそう...
Looks like we could project 2D on the paintings...
私がね、そら先輩のライブで壁面参加しましたけれども。
I did a wall participation in Sora-senpai's live.
そうだね、ライブ2D写せそうだね。
Yeah, we could project Live2D.
なんか今後あったら面白いよね、ホーンテッドマンションみたいで。
It'd be funny if we did that, like the Haunted Mansion.
ということで、ここでねちょっと色んな写真を撮っていこうかなと思うんですが...
Anyway, I want to take some photos here,
...何やらゲストが来てくれてるみたいなので...
...but it seems a guest has arrived,
...ちょっとゲスト呼びたいと思います。
...so I'll call them out.
私もねゲスト誰なんだか分からないんだけど...
I don't even know who the guest is...
うん、じゃあちょっと呼んでみますか。
...well, let's call them.
誰だ？
Who is it?
あ、ゲストの人なのかゲストの子なのか、誰なんだ？
Is it a guest person or a guest kid? Who is it?
はい。
Okay.
あれれ？なんか...ん？
Huh? What...?
あら！あらあらあらあら！
Oh! My! Oh my!
あ、ルイ友さん！
Ah, Luitomo!
あ、ルイ友さんも3D化しちゃったみたいですね。
It looks like Luitomo has gone 3D too.
はい、ということでお誕生日の時6月11日のね生誕祭の時に...
Even though I only just revealed the design
...デザインを公開したばかりなのに...
...on my birthday celebration on June 11,
...もう3Dにルイ友さんなっちゃいました。
...Luitomo is already 3D.
ということでルイ友さんも含めてねちょっと写真を撮りたいなと思うんですが...
So I want to take photos with Luitomo as well.
ちょっとソファ座ってもいいかな？
Is it okay if I sit on the sofa?
ソファ座ります。よいしょ。
I'm sitting down. There we go.
はい。よいしょ。
Yes. Up we go.
いやーいいですね。どうですか？ソファ似合う？
This is great. How is it? Does the sofa suit me?
いや、このソファもね、めちゃくちゃこだわって作ってもらったのよ。おしゃれでしょ？
This sofa was also custom-made with a lot of care. It's stylish, right?
あ、なんか様になってるね。
Oh, it looks quite good on me.
トゥルルン、ドゥン、ドゥン、トゥルルン、ドゥン、ドゥン。
Tu-ru-run, dun, dun, tu-ru-run, dun, dun.
はい、鷹嶺ルイの部屋、始まりました。
All right, Takane Lui's Room is now in session.
本日のゲストはルイ友さんです！
Today's guests are the Lui-tomos!
それではね、ルイ友さん呼んで... あ、ちょっと...
Now then, let's call the Lui-tomos... Oh, wait...
大丈夫？ なんか盛り上がってる？ ルイ友さん、大丈夫？
Are you guys okay? Are you excited? Lui-tomos, you all right?
あ、ルイ友さんもね、座りたいか？
Oh, do you Lui-tomos want to sit down too?
じゃ、ちょっと座る？ お膝に座ろうか。
Then, want to sit? How about sitting on my lap?
最初に関...
First, I'll...
えー...
Uh...
じゃ、女の子の方。
Let's go with the girl first.
よいしょ！
Up we go!
はい、えーっと...
There we go...
はい、お膝に乗って偉いねー。
Good job sitting on my lap.
よしよしよしよしよし、可愛い！
There, there, there... You're so cute!
可愛いなー。
So cute.
今日は見に来てくれてありがとうね。
Thanks for coming to see me today.
で、ちょっとじゃ、座っててもらって...
Now, please sit there for a bit...
男の子のルイ友さん、おいで。
Boy Lui-tomo, come here.
よいしょ！
Up we go!
はい、どう？ 私のお膝の座り心地はどうだい？
So, how is it? How's the view from my lap?
よしよしよしよし... あ、ちょっとジタバタしないの。ちょっと...
There, there... Hey, don't squirm. Wait...
ジタバタする悪い子はお仕置きがあるよ。大丈夫？
Naughty boys who squirm get punished. Are you ready?
ちょっと、ジタバタしない！
Hey, stop squirming!
もみもみじゃないのよ。
No rubbing!
い... 可愛い可愛い。
Ca... So cute, so cute.
ね、ということで一緒に座って...
Anyway, let's sit together...
あ、どうですか？ い... 一緒に座れたね。
How's this? We're... sitting together now.
お！ ホークアイモードになった。
Oh! You've entered Hawk Eye mode.
お！ え？ 嘘！ 君たちもホークアイモードになるだと？
Oh! What? No way! You guys can enter Hawk Eye mode too?
じゃおそろだ。おそろでじゃ、はいチーズ！
Then we're matching. Matching, all right, say cheese!
どうかな？ 写真撮れた？ うまく。
How was it? Did you get a good photo?
じゃあね、先ほどなんかコメントにもあった、ちょっとお仕置きをねしてくださいっていう人が...
Now then, there were some comments earlier asking for a punishment...
結構多いみたいなので...
Since there seem to be quite a few...
じゃあお仕置き、しょうがないからしてあげようかな。うん。
I guess I'll have to give you a punishment. Yeah.
ということでさっき悪さをしたルイ友はどっちだ？
So, which Lui-tomo was being naughty earlier?
どっちだ？ ほい、出てきなさい。
Which one? Come on, step forward.
あ、そっぽ向いてんじゃいよ、そっぽ。こっちに来なさい。こっちに、はいおいで。
Hey, don't look away. Don't look away. Come here. Come here.
「俺？」うんうんじゃないのよ。はい、来なさい、来なさい。
"Me?" Don't "uh-huh" me. Come here, come here.
じゃあね、ちょっと女の子には痛いと思うから...
Well, I think it'll be too painful for the girl, so...
よし、行くぞ！ えい！
All right, here it comes! Take that!
痛いか？
Does it hurt?
さっきはよくももみもみしやがって。おい！
How dare you keep rubbing me like that! Hey!
えい！ えい！ えい！
Take that! And that! And that!
ちょっと、なんか優しい、優しい感じにしちゃったけど、もっと欲しいのかい？
I might have been a bit too gentle. Do you want more?
なんか喜んでる、喜んでるんだけど大丈夫？
You seem to be enjoying it... Are you okay?
じゃあちょっと、画面の向こうのみんなにもお仕置きしちゃおうかな。
Now, I think I'll punish everyone on the other side of the screen too.
えい！ なんかエロイこと考えて...
Take that! Thinking about dirty things...
賢者とか言ってサジェスト荒らしたのは誰だ、どこのどいつなんだよ！ これこれこれこれこれ！
Who's the one who messed up the search suggestions with words like "Sage"! Hey, hey, hey!
早く「#3D」って呟いて、サジェストを3Dまみれにしろ！ おいおいおいおいおい！
Hurry up and tweet "#3D" to flood the suggestions with 3D! Come on, come on!
ということでね、なんかトレンド、トレンド？ 結構いい感じのトレンドになったみたいなんですね。
Anyway, it looks like we've managed to trend quite well.
あ、1位！ ありがとうございます！ これでサジェスト賢者なくなるよね。
Oh, #1! Thank you so much! This should get rid of the "Sage" suggestions.
まあね、ちょっと「賢者って何のことやねん」って方はね、ぜひぜひ、あの、切り抜きだったりとかも回ってますのでね...
For those wondering "What's this 'Sage' thing?", there are clips floating around, so...
見ていただければなと思います。
Please check them out.
ということで、今度はステージの方に行きましょうか。うん。
With that, shall we head over to the stage now? Yes.
ステージの方に、レッツゴー！
To the stage, let's go!
あ、こっちか。あ、こっちからだ。
Oh, this way? Ah, it's from here.
うわああ！
Whoa!
ということでこのステージ、いかがですか？
So, how do you like this stage?
結構広々としてるでしょう？
It's quite spacious, isn't it?
さっき見た感じだと「ちょっと狭いのかな」って思った人もいるかもしれないですが...
Some of you might have thought it looked a bit cramped earlier, but...
そう、広いんですよ。
That's right, it's actually quite large.
ということでここでね、ちょっと...
So, here...
みんなにサービスを、私のさ、ちょっと可愛いお顔見てほしくて...
I want to give you all some fan service. I want you to see my cute face...
ちょっとガチ恋距離しても大丈夫？ ガチ恋距離。
Is it okay if I get really close? Close enough to fall in love.
えーっと...
Let's see...
ど... どう？ このカメラで行く？
Ho... How's this? Should we go with this camera?
こっち...
This way...
さっきの、なんかガチ恋カメラないかな？
I wonder if that 'serious love' camera from earlier is available?
さっきのありますかね？
Is it available?
はい。ちょっとね、待っていただければ...
Yes. If you could wait a moment...
...とっても可愛い、映えな写真が撮れるみたいなので...
...it seems like you can take very cute, 'Insta-worthy' photos...
待っていきましょう。みんな何々？
Let's wait for it. What's everyone saying?
「助かる」「美しい」「可愛い」そうでしょ。
'This helps,' 'Beautiful,' 'Cute.' I know, right?
あ、カメラいけるみたいなんで。
Oh, looks like the camera is ready.
よし、ガチ恋距離！どうですか？
Alright, 'serious love' distance! How is it?
ん？可愛いでしょ？
Hm? I'm cute, aren't I?
はい。
Yes.
うんうんうん、なんかみんな満足してくれてる？
Mhm, is everyone satisfied?
はい。
Yes.
え、このカメラマジで盛れる。
Wow, this camera really makes me look good.
すでにさ、可愛いんだけどさ、なんか1.5割増しで可愛くない？
I'm already cute, but don't I look like 15% cuter?
どうですかね？いっぱい写真撮れた？
How was it? Did you take lots of photos?
うんうん。
Mhm.
ありがとうございます。きれい。可愛い。
Thank you. 'Beautiful,' 'Cute.'
ありがとう、めちゃくちゃ嬉しい。
Thank you, I'm so happy.
ということで、ガチ恋距離もね、終わったところで。
And with that, now that we're done with the close-ups...
な、何やら、あれ？
Wh-what is this? Huh?
なんか、このステージで何をするのかって言いますと、
As for what I'll be doing on this stage,
この配信でね、あの、サムネにも書いてありました
During this stream, as mentioned in the thumbnail,
重大告知をしたいなって思うんですけれども、
I'd like to make a major announcement,
なんか、普通に重大告知させてくれたらいいのにさ、
I wish they'd just let me announce it normally,
なんか、この発表をかけて企画にね、挑戦しないといけないらしくて。
but apparently, I have to clear a challenge for this announcement.
まあ、その企画ちょっと私腑に落ちないんだけど、
Well, I'm not quite sure about this challenge, but...
じゃあ、ちょっと企画名、ちょっと言わせていただきます。
...let me say the name of the challenge.
その企画は、全力ジェスチャーゲーム！
The challenge is: All-out Gesture Game!
なんでジェスチャーゲームしなきゃいけないんだ。
Why do I have to play a gesture game?
はい、ということで、これからね、私にはジェスチャーのお題が5問出されるみたいです、5問。
Alright, so I'll be given 5 gesture prompts, 5 of them.
で、そのお題に対して30秒間で私が全力で、もう、この3D、手に入れた3Dをね、駆使して、全力で、
And for each prompt, I'll have 30 seconds to use this 3D body I've gained to the fullest,
全力で、全力でジェスチャーをして、
and give it my all performing gestures,
で、これから呼ぶ助っ人が5問中3問答えてくれたらクリアで、
and if the helpers I'm about to call can answer 3 out of 5 correctly, I clear it,
告知することができると。普通に告知させてくれよ！
and I can make the announcement. Just let me announce it normally!
っていう、なんかチャレンジがあるので、
So, since there's this challenge,
まあ、ちょっと告知できないのは残念なのでね、告知をかけて全力ジェスチャーをしていきたいと思います。
and it would be a shame not to announce it, I'll do my best at the gesture game for the sake of the announcement.
はい、ということで私も頑張るんだけど、やっぱりさ、答えてくれる助っ人が誰かによりますよね。
Alright, I'll do my best, but it really depends on who the helpers are, right?
ね、ルイ友さんだったら私のことさ、わかってくれてるんじゃないかなと思うので、ルイ友さんだったらいいなって
I think the Ruitomo (fans) would understand me well, so I thought it would be great if it was them,
言ったら、ルイ友さんはダメらしいくて。
but apparently, the Ruitomo aren't allowed.
なので、まあ、私のことを知っている、もう知り尽くしているメンバーといえば、
So, if we're talking about members who know me inside and out,
そう、HoloXのメンバーですね。
yes, it's the members of HoloX.
なので、呼びたいと思います。強力な助っ人、カモン！
So, I'd like to call them out. Powerful helpers, come on!
どうもどうもどうも！
Hello, hello, hello!
こんばんは！HoloXのメンバー、あれ？なんか、あれ？一人足りないけど、まあ...
Good evening! The members of HoloX... wait, huh? One person is missing, but well...
気のせい。
You're imagining it.
気のせい。あ、じゃあ、一人ずつ挨拶してもらってもいいかな？
Imagining it? Ah, well, can you each introduce yourselves?
刮目せよ！お仕置きくださいです。
Behold! Please give me a punishment.
どういうこと？
What do you mean by that?
後でビシビシやってあげるよ。
I'll give it to you good later.
気持ちいい！
Feels good!
はい、じゃあ、あの、ちゃんと頑張って答えてね。
Alright, well, make sure you do your best to answer.
任せろ。
Leave it to me.
頼むよ。
I'm counting on you.
はい、こんさかよ！ホロライブ6期生HoloXのズンドコバチコイ掃除屋、沙花叉クロヱでございます。お仕置きくださいです。
Yes, hello! I am Sakamata Chloe, the 'zundoko-bachikoi' cleaner of Hololive Gen 6, HoloX. Please give me a punishment.
あ、なんか、今日がお披露目なのに、明日がお披露目だって、なんか告知したい人がいるみたい...
Ah, even though today is my debut, it seems like someone wants to announce that tomorrow is theirs...
待って待って待って！
Wait, wait, wait!
お仕置きが必要かな？
I guess a punishment is in order?
あ、え、でも、鞭で叩いてくれるなら、それはそれでちょっと嬉しいかも...
Ah, well, if you hit me with a whip, I might actually be a little happy...
ダメ！バカ犬の鞭！
No! Stupid dog's whip!
ラプより先にやってもらっちゃうもんね。
I'll get it before Lap-sama does.
じゃあ、後でね、ピチピチとお尻を叩いてやりたいなと思うんですけど、この中で、まあ私はね、この三人の中で一番変態なんじゃないかって思っている、いろは。
Well, I'll give your butts a good slapping later, but among them, I think Iroha might be the biggest pervert of the three.
おいこら！ということで、こんばんはでござる。ホロライブ6期生HoloXの用心棒、侍、風真いろはでござる。
Hey! Anyway, good evening. I am Kazama Iroha, the samurai bodyguard of Hololive Gen 6, HoloX.
別に叩いてほしいとか言わないでござるが...
I didn't say I wanted to be hit or anything...
これがいいんだろ、これが。
You like this, don't you?
あ！出た！あ、ごめんなさい、え、わ、待って！いや、べ...
Ah! There it is! Ah, sorry, wait! No, I...
やっぱりそう言うやつだったんだ。
So she's that kind of person after all.
やめて、やめてってこと？
You mean like, "Stop it, stop it"?
はい。あれ、一人足りなくない？
Right. Wait, isn't someone missing?
お、お、寝坊したとかじゃないよね？
Oh, she didn't oversleep or anything, right?
ちゃんと見てくれてるよね？私の3D。
She's watching my 3D stream, right?
あいつは我々の心の中に...
She's here, in our hearts...
なんか居なくなったって言うのやめてよ。生きてるからね。
Stop talking like she's gone. She's alive, you know.
ということで、じゃあ三人も、ちょっと腑に落ちないけど、
Anyway, so the three of you... even though it's a bit unsettling,
三人とも自信のほどは、自信のほどはどうですか？
how's your confidence level? How are you feeling?
おー、任せな、ルイ。ねー、任せてござるよ。
Oh, leave it to us, Lui! You can count on me!
お前のことなら何でも分かるよ。
I know everything about you.
まあ、何千年も寄り添いましたからね。
Well, we've been together for thousands of years.
分かってくれないと困っちゃうんですけど。
I'd be in trouble if you didn't understand me.
何千年！？何千年、やってんな。
Thousands of years!? You've been at it for that long?
あ、でも本当に、正解しないと、
But really, if you don't get the answers right,
実はこのメンバーの中の重大告知もあるので、
one of the members actually has a major announcement to make,
ぜひぜひ頑張っていただかないと困るんですよ。
so I really need you to do your best.
やるぞ！頑張ろう！頑張ってください。頑張るでござるよ。
Let's do it! Let's do our best! Good luck! I'll do my best!
じゃあ、早速始めましょうか。
Then, let's get started right away.
はい。はい。お題は私と今ね、
Yes! Yes! The prompt will only be shown to me
見てくださっている配信を、配信を見てくださっている方々だけにでます。
and the viewers who are watching the stream right now.
HoloXメンバーには出ません。なので、
The HoloX members won't see it. So,
配信閉じるぞ！閉じるぞ！ちゃんと閉じて、閉じて。
I'll close the stream! Closing it! Make sure you close it.
それでは、準備はいいかな？
Now then, are you ready?
オッケー！はい。いつでも来いよ。
Okay! Yes! Bring it on anytime!
ということで、全力ジェスチャー一問目、スタート！
So, here's the first full-power gesture question! Start!
お題：女幹部
Prompt: Female Executive
あ、こいつは始まるんや。あ、始まってる。
Ah, it's about to start. Oh, it's started.
おー？えー？何だ？何？
Oh? Eh? What is it? What?
決めポーズ！アイドル！
A signature pose! Idol!
アイドルじゃない。え？幹部？自分？
Not an idol. Eh? Executive? Yourself?
分かった！分かった！分かった！分かった！女幹部！
Got it! I got it! I know! Female Executive!
あー！正解！すごい！やったー！わー！
Ah! Correct! Amazing! Yay! Wow!
天才！え、30秒以内だったよね？
Genius! It was within 30 seconds, right?
うふ。え、え、何で分かったの、今ので？
Haha. Wait, how did you know from that?
え、いや、なんかあの「自分、自分」って出てたから、うーんと思って、
Well, you were pointing at yourself, and I thought...
あのいつも自己紹介の時にやるポーズがやってたから、
since you did that pose you always do in your self-introduction,
「女幹部か！」と思って。
I thought, "Ah, Female Executive!"
いや、もう流石だな。天才でござるな。
Wow, as expected. You're a genius!
いや、こよりといろはも、ちょっと惜しいところまで言ってたんだけどね。
Koyori and Iroha were also very close.
そうね。届かなかったね。ね。
Yeah. We didn't quite reach it.
ふふ。ま、ルイ姉といえば女幹部でござるからな。そうだよ。
Haha. Well, Lui-nee is synonymous with Female Executive. That's true.
じゃあ、この調子で二問目いけるかな？
Then, can we do the second question with this momentum?
オッケー！任せな！任せてござるよ。
Okay! Leave it to us! Count on me!
順調だからね。これでストレート勝ちしよう。
We're doing well. Let's aim for a straight-win victory.
オッケー。何に負けるな。行くぞ。
Okay. Don't lose to anything! Let's go!
負け。行くぞ、二問目、スタート！
Don't lose! Here we go, second question, start!
お題：酔っ払い
Prompt: Drunkard
あ。お？え？あっち？あ、酔っ払い！
Ah. Oh? Eh? That way? Ah, a drunkard!
酔っ払い！あー！正解！
A drunkard! Ah! Correct!
すごい！すごい！やったー！
Amazing! Great job! Yay!
えー、よく分かったね。なんか酔ってる感じがした。
Wow, you got that fast. You really looked drunk.
すごいでござるな。最初綺麗にフラッてしてたから
That's amazing. At first, you were swaying so nicely
バリデーションかなんかと思ったけど、なんかフラフラしてたな。
that I thought it was some kind of validation, but you were wobbling.
思いの外、綺麗に酔っちゃったから。
I acted drunk more elegantly than I intended.
ああ、流石ね、綺麗でござるな。
Ah, as expected. Your movements were so graceful.
動きがね、ちょっと綺麗すぎるんだな。
Your movements are just a bit too beautiful.
やっぱり私、なんかこういうジェスチャーゲームとか得意なのかもしれない。
Maybe I'm actually gifted at these gesture games.
うん。我が輩の理解力かもしれん。
Or maybe it's my incredible comprehension skills.
確かにね。動きめっちゃ綺麗だからね。
True. Your movements are very clean.
ね。そうなんでござる。華があるでござる。
Right. You really have that flair.
えー、嬉しい。じゃあ、もう、あれ？
Oh, I'm so happy. Then, wait?
三問正解したらいいみたいだから、次で！
It seems like three correct answers are enough, so let's finish with the next one!
二人共、二人共、次答えて、二人共。
Both of you, I want both of you to answer the next one.
答えろ、答えろ。頑張れ、頑張れ。
Answer it! Answer it! Good luck!
こよりといろは、いくよ。
Koyori and Iroha, here we go.
行くぜ。三問目、スタート！
Let's go! Third question, start!
お題：ビジネスマン
Prompt: Businessman
ん。あ。迷ってるんだ。
Hmm. Oh. She's hesitating.
迷ってんだ。え？何？
She's struggling. Eh? What is it?
パソコン。OL。二人共頑張れ。
A laptop? Office lady? Both of you, do your best!
OLじゃないの？え、会社員？
Isn't it office lady? Eh, company employee?
社畜？社畜？え、社畜？
A corporate drone? A wage slave? Eh, wage slave?
何？会社じゃないの？バリバリ？
What? Not a company? Hardworking business person?
あ、あ、惜しい！惜しい！
Ah, ah, so close! So close!
ビジネスマンとか？
Is it a businessman or something?
あー！すごい！やったー！
Ah! You got it! Amazing! Yay!
え、何で分かった、え？何で閉まってるので分かった？
Wait, how did you know? Why did you know from that motion?
閉まって、なんか出して、シュシュシュってしてたので分かった。
I knew because you were putting things away, taking things out, and typing away.
これは、私もう絶対ダメだと思ってた。
I honestly thought this one was impossible for you.
なー、え、ちょっと。やりおるな。ちょっと舐めすぎでしょ。
Wow, wait. You're actually good. I underestimated you guys too much.
流石ですよ。舐めすぎだよ。
As expected of us. You definitely underestimated us.
えー、すごい。ストレートで成功ということで。
Wow, amazing. A straight-win victory for all of you.
ストレートで。ナイス。いや、もう負けたくなかったんですけど。
A straight win! Nice! Honestly, I really didn't want to lose.
四問目、五問目やらなくて済んだわ。ありがとう。
Now I don't have to do questions four or five. Thank you.
なん、やったー！
We did it! Yay!
ということで、じゃあ告知。ご褒美の告知タイムにいきましょうか。
So then, onto the announcement. Let's move to the reward announcement time.
イェーイ！ということで、まずはちょっとみんなにもいてもらって。
Yay! Alright, first, I'll have everyone stay with me here.
まずはおさらいです。
First, a recap.
ドン！
Bam!
誕生日記念 2022
Birthday Commemoration 2022
はい、鷹嶺ルイの6月11日に発売しました誕生日記念のグッズがまだまだ発売中でございます。
Yes, Takane Lui's birthday commemorative goods, which went on sale on June 11th, are still available.
フルセットには、
In the full set...
あ、めちゃめちゃいいでしょ。
Oh, it's really good, right?
うん！
Yeah!
フルセットには私の直筆サインがついていまして、あの、数量限定なわけではありませんので、
The full set comes with my handwritten signature, and it's not a limited quantity item,
ぜひぜひね、7月入ってからちょっと「今日はお金がちょっとやばいわ」みたいなね、方に関しましては7月に入ってからでも全然大丈夫なので、
So please, even for those who are like "My money is a bit tight today," it's perfectly fine to get it after July starts,
あの、よかったら買っていただければなと思います。はい。ラインナップはこちら。
so I'd be happy if you could buy it. Here's the lineup.
いやどうですか？
So, how is it?
ドン！
Bam!
ワイングラス欲しい！
I want the wine glass!
ワイングラス欲しいね。
We want the wine glass, don't we?
晩酌配信にもいいし、しかもお酒飲めない方はなんか小物入れとかにもできるおしゃれなワイングラスにしてみたので。
It's good for evening drink streams, and for those who don't drink alcohol, I made it a stylish wine glass that can also be used as a small accessory case.
ね。あとはま、がんもですね。結構人気ながんもキーホルダーも。
Right. And then, Ganmo. The quite popular Ganmo keychain too.
え、がんも可愛い！
Eh, Ganmo is so cute!
一緒にがんも連れて歩けるので、よかったら買っていただけたらなと思います。
You can walk around with Ganmo, so I hope you'll buy it.
いいね。
Nice.
あと記念ボイスはね、私がシナリオを担当させていただきましたので、よかったら聞いてください。
Also, for the memorial voice, I was in charge of the scenario, so please give it a listen.
どんなん？デートやん実質。
What's it like? It's practically a date.
デートだよ。よかったら後でちょっと渡すから聞いて。
It is a date. I'll give it to you later, so listen to it.
買うんで大丈夫です。
I'll buy it, so it's okay.
あ、買うの？買ってくれんの？
Oh, you're buying it? You're going to buy it for me?
買うんで大丈夫です。
I'll buy it, so it's okay.
いや、それは嬉しいけど。
Well, that makes me happy, though.
よし、じゃあ続いては…
Alright, then next...
誰の告知だ？ドゥルルルルルルルル…ドン！
Whose announcement is it? (Drumroll)... Bam!
はい！ラプラス・ダークネスが重大告知が明日19時にあるみたいですね。
Yes! It seems La+ Darknesss has a major announcement tomorrow at 19:00.
ラプ、明日19時に重大告知、私聞いてないんだけど。
Lapu, I didn't hear about a major announcement tomorrow at 19:00.
まあ、ありますね。これね。
Well, there is one. This.
まあ、暇だったら見に来てください。
Well, if you're free, come watch.
いや、みんな見に来るよ、きっと。
No, everyone will come to watch, I'm sure.
本当？
Really?
来てくれたら嬉しいね。
It'd be great if they come.
どんなこと告知するんだ？
What are you going to announce?
なん、なんだろうね。
Wha- what could it be?
え、このシルエットは何？もしかして新衣装？新衣装かも。
Eh, what's this silhouette? Maybe a new outfit? Could be a new outfit.
お、なんだろうね。まあまあ、ちょっと流れを、流れを理解すればもうわかるんじゃないかな。
Oh, what could it be? Well, well, I think you'll understand if you just follow the flow.
なんかこれ並んだらなんか、あ、ちょっとやめましょうね。
If these are lined up like this, oh, let's stop that.
はい次、次、次。
Okay, next, next, next.
はい！ということで皆さん 6月22日、明日ですね。明日の19時にラプラスのチャンネルで重大告知配信がありますので、ぜひぜひ見に行ってください。
Yes! So, everyone, June 22nd, that's tomorrow. Tomorrow at 19:00, there will be a major announcement stream on La+'s channel, so please go watch it.
よろしくお願いします！みんなで見るぞ！
Please look forward to it! We'll all watch it!
3人ともありがとう。ちょっとクロヱは締めといて。うん。
Thanks, you three. Chloe, handle the wrap-up. Yeah.
オッケー！オッケー！
Okay! Okay!
裏に沈めとくね。
I'll sink her in the back.
ありがとう。ということで3人でした！ありがとう！
Thanks. So, that was the three of them! Thank you!
またねー！またねー！見ててねー！
See ya! See ya! Keep watching!
はい。
Yes.
ということで重大告知の前に、私、あの、やり忘れたこと1つあって。これやらないと悔いが残るのでやってもいいですか？やっていいです。
So, before the major announcements, there's one thing I forgot to do. I'll regret it if I don't do this, so can I do it? I will do it.
えーと、私といえば、そう、あのホロックスの女幹部なんですけれども、宝鐘海賊団のエロ女幹部でもあるので、あれをやっておかないとなっていうことでやらせていただければなと思います。
Um, speaking of me, yes, I'm a Holox female executive, but I'm also the "sexy female executive" of the Houshou Pirates, so I feel like I have to do that.
いくぞ！
Here I go!
アホイ！
Ahoi!
え、ホロライブ6期生、
Eh, Hololive 6th gen,
宝鐘海賊団エロ女幹部の鷹嶺ルイです！
Houshou Pirates' sexy female executive, Takane Lui!
どう？よかった。
How was it? Good.
最初にやろうと思ってたんだけどさ、緊張でちょっと飛んでしまいまして。やらせていただきました。
I was planning to do it at the beginning, but it totally slipped my mind because of the nerves. I did it.
どう、どう、どう、エロ、エロかった？
How, how, how? Was it... was it sexy?
はい。ということで、もう、はい。それでは重大告知、いきます！
Yes. So, okay, yes. Now then, major announcements, here we go!
はい、ここから重大告知です。本日この配信終了後にこちら！
Yes, from here on are the major announcements. Today, after this stream ends, this!
はい、先ほども歌わせていただきました『キミソラキセキ』がね、投稿されます、プレミア公開されます。
Yes, "Kimi Sora Kiseki", which I sang earlier, will be posted, it'll have a premiere.
はい。この21時ちょっと過ぎかな？にプレミア公開されるのでぜひぜひ見に行ってください。
Yes. It'll be premiered just after 21:00, so please go watch it.
続いてこちら。はい、本日23時から、メン限配信をさせていただきます。
Next is this. Yes, starting today at 23:00, I'll be doing a membership-only stream.
おうち3Dでね、打ち上げ晩酌をやらせていただこうかなと思いますので、今日メンバーに入った方、ぜひぜひ楽しみにしてててください。
I'm thinking of doing an after-party evening drink stream in "Home 3D", so those who joined the membership today, please look forward to it.
そしてそして、次が待ちに待ったあの発表です。ドン！
And then, and then, next is the long-awaited announcement. Bam!
はい！ということでお誕生日の時にお話がありました…
Yes! So, there was some talk during my birthday...
柊キライ先生に書いていただきました、
Written by Hiiragi Kirai-sensei,
「オーバード」というオリジナル曲が、
an original song called "Overbird"...
本日24時に各種音楽サイトで配信されます！
...will be available on various music streaming sites at midnight tonight!
うわー！
Waaaa!
いやもうさ、かっこいい、かっこいいって好評で。
Wow, people are already praising it as "cool" and "awesome."
もう本当に嬉しいです。
I'm really happy about it.
私もね、めちゃくちゃ気に入ってる楽曲なので、
It's a song I really like as well,
ぜひぜひみんなにもたくさん聴いてもらいたいなということで、
so I definitely want everyone to listen to it a lot.
3Dおめでとうっていう気持ちでね、
In the spirit of celebrating my 3D debut,
ぜひぜひ24時に買っていただければなと思います。
I hope you'll check it out at 24:00.
そして、このMVと、あと振付の...
And then, the music video and the choreography for...
TikTokなんかも後日投稿させていただきますので、
TikTok will also be posted at a later date,
楽しみにしててくださーい！
so please look forward to those!
そして、本日はこの「オーバード」を、
And today, ahead of its digital release,
配信に先駆けて初披露させていただきます！
I will be performing "Overbird" for the first time!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ということで、オリジナル曲「オーバード」なんですけれども、
So, about the original song "Overbird"...
この曲はね、あの、女幹部の、
this song is about a female executive's...
表向きの女幹部のお仕事と、
public-facing professional life...
あと裏にある私の気持ちみたいな、
and the feelings she keeps hidden.
ちょっとそういったギャップを書いてもらった、
It's written with that kind of "gap" in mind,
闇の...闇？ちょっとダークチックな歌詞になってますので、
with somewhat dark... or should I say "shadowy" lyrics.
ぜひぜひ楽しみに聴いていただけたらなと思うんですが、
I hope you enjoy listening to it.
24時に配信の音源とは、これから歌うので違うので、
Since this is a live performance, it'll be different from the studio version.
そういったちょっと音源の聴き比べもね、
So, I'd be happy if you could compare
してくださったら嬉しいです！
the live and recorded versions!
ということで、いきましょうか、早速！
Anyway, let's get started right away!
はい、ということで、オリジナル曲「オーバード」、
All right then, here is my original song "Overbird".
ぜひ聴いてください！
Please listen!
オーバード
作詞・作曲：柊キライ
Overbird
Lyrics/Composition: Hiiragi Kirai
四六時中　帰りの会で
Round the clock, at the dismissal meeting
面倒くささを押し付けられてる
I'm being forced to deal with tedious things
何から何まで
From start to finish
死語はやめて　まとめ役なら
Stop using dead words; as the coordinator
機嫌を上手に宥めている
I'm skillfully smoothing things over
仲良しこよしで
Playing pretend friends
さだだだだ　黙れ溜まり給えよ
Sha-da-da-da-da, shut up and stay put
言えないね　そんな強い言葉は
I can't say such harsh words
少しだけ静かにしてほしいね　あー
I just want you to be a little quiet, ah
私たち大暴走
We're running wildly out of control
世界征服　イェイイェイイェイ
World domination, yay yay yay
果たすその日まで
Until the day it's achieved
全霊全酷　イェイイェイイェイ
Total devotion, total cruelty, yay yay yay
あなたの周りも
Even everyone around you
世界征服　アレ、アレ、ア
World domination, ale, ale, a
約束の地まで
To the promised land
さあ掲げよ　バッテンバッテン
Now raise it up, cross, cross
テンデンプク　イェイイェイイェイ
Topsy-turvy, yay yay yay
今日も期待　そっちのけだね
Expectations ignored again today
嫌になるから　私一人でも
I'm sick of it, so even if I'm alone
やっておきますね
I'll get it done
全て全て全て任せて
Leave it all, all, all to me
それをさせてよ　大事なことなの
Let me do it; it's important
分かっているでしょう
You surely understand
四六時中　帰りの会で
Round the clock, at the dismissal meeting
面倒くさいまま　今日も明日も
Tediously, today and tomorrow too
過ぎて行くのでしょう
Will probably just pass by
花瓶に水をあげましょう
Let's water the flower vase
時の中　萎れたこと忘れてた
I'd forgotten that they'd withered over time
さだだだだ　黙れ溜まり給えよ
Sha-da-da-da-da, shut up and stay put
言えないね　そんな強い言葉は
I can't say such harsh words
少しだけ静かにしてほしいね　あー
I just want you to be a little quiet, ah
私たち大暴走
We're running wildly out of control
今と見えない　見たかったはずなのに
Unseen now, even though I wanted to see it
世界征服　イェイイェイイェイ
World domination, yay yay yay
見えぬその日まで
Until that unseen day
どどどどど　えーえーえー
Do-do-do-do-do, eh-eh-eh
この世の理
The law of this world
今は征征征　さささささ
Now conquer, conquer, conquer, sa-sa-sa
あなたの真逆
Your exact opposite
形作ればバッテン
If I form it, it's a cross
世界征服　イェイイェイイェイ
World domination, yay yay yay
果たすその日まで
Until the day it's achieved
全霊全酷　イェイイェイイェイ
Total devotion, total cruelty, yay yay yay
あなたの周りも
Even everyone around you
世界征服　アレ、アレ、ア
World domination, ale, ale, a
約束の地まで
To the promised land
さあ掲げよ　バッテンバッテン
Now raise it up, cross, cross
テンデンプク
Topsy-turvy
ヒタラビン　ビンテージのワイン分けましょう
Let's share some vintage wine
ここへ跪け！
Kneel before me here!
吐いて捨てるような現実は
A reality you'd just spit out and discard,
断固両断 叩き切る
I'll decisively cut it in two.
終わりなき輪廻に迷いし 業よ
O Karma, lost in an endless cycle of rebirth.
漆黒の翼で 誘おう
I shall invite you with jet-black wings.
我らエデンの星を統べる者
We are the rulers of the star Eden,
秘密結社
Secret Society
holoX！
holoX!
いつも思うのは、不器用だなってこと
What I always think is that you're clumsy.
人一倍努力をして、時には自分を犠牲にしてでも、
Working harder than anyone else, sometimes even sacrificing yourself,
誰かのために頑張れるのが貴方の凄いところ。
being able to do your best for someone else is what's amazing about you.
その優しさに、私を含めた皆が支えられているし、
Everyone, including me, is supported by that kindness,
貴方自身も誰かの笑顔に安堵していると思う。
and I think you yourself find peace in someone's smile.
今日も自分の周りの人が少しでも幸せでよかったって。
Thinking, "I'm glad the people around me were even a little bit happy today."
でも、私はそんな貴方を見ていて不安になります。
But, watching you like that makes me feel anxious.
いつも笑って、困っている人には親身に寄り添い、
Always smiling, being close to those in trouble,
人のために怒ったり悲しんだりできる。
being able to get angry or sad for others.
頼れるルイ姉になってしまう貴方は、
You, who becomes the reliable 'Lui-nee',
本当に無理をしていないですか？
aren't you really pushing yourself too hard?
誰かのために自分のやりたかった事、言いたかった事、
For someone else's sake, aren't you swallowing and suppressing
本当は我慢したくない事を飲み込み、押し殺してないかな？
the things you wanted to do, or the things you really didn't want to endure?
貴方は自分の心を後回しに明るく振舞うけど、
You behave brightly while putting your own heart last, but
本当はとても繊細で人の機微に聡く、
I know that you are actually very delicate, sensitive to subtleties,
抱え込みやすい事を知っています。
and prone to taking everything on yourself.
無理をするなと言われても、無理してしまうのも知っています。
I know that you'll keep pushing yourself even if told not to.
だから変わってほしいなんて言わない。
So I won't say I want you to change.
でも今日だけは、ありのままの貴方で楽しんでほしい。
But for today only, I want you to enjoy being yourself.
誰かのためでなく、貴方だけのために貴方自身を輝かせてほしい。
I want you to shine for yourself, not for anyone else.
貴方も同じアイドルなんだよ。遠慮なんてしていいんだよ。
You're an idol too. You don't have to hold back.
傍で見てきた沢山の努力たちは、全て報われていいものだったのだから。
Because all the effort I've seen by your side deserves to be rewarded.
だから今ここで私達に見せてほしい。
So please, show us right here.
貴方が本当に望む貴方を。
The you that you truly desire to be.
貴方の軌跡と貴方が描く未来を。
Your trajectory and the future you envision.
はい。
Yes.
クロヱ、ありがとう。
Chloe, thank you.
いやー、泣いちまった。
Man, I ended up crying.
やばいやばい、ちょっとあのスタッフさんにティッシュ持ってきてもらったんだけど、
Oh man, I had the staff bring me some tissues,
全然足りないんだけど、ティッシュ。
but they're not enough at all.
本当にありがとう。
Truly, thank you.
まあ私なんかがアイドルなんてって自分でも思っていたんですが、
Well, I used to think, "How could someone like me be an idol?"
やっぱりホロライブに入ったからには
But since I joined Hololive after all,
歌って踊れるアーティスト、そしてアイドルになりたいなと思って、
I wanted to become an artist and idol who can sing and dance,
自信がついた時にはこの曲を歌おうと思ってました。
and I planned to sing this song once I gained confidence.
なので是非、あのー、
So please, um,
ホロのオリジナル曲今まで歌ってこなかったんですけども、
I haven't sung any Holo original songs until now,
初めて歌うならこの曲と決めていた曲、是非聴いてください。
but this is the one I decided to sing first. Please listen.
いきます。
Here I go.
キラメキライダー☆
Kirameki Rider☆
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make these fresh heartbeats resonate
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
In the best of times, with the best of friends
キラメキにのって
Riding on the sparkle
覚えてるかな 最初の歌
Do you remember? That very first song
私の声が震えていた
When my voice was trembling
あの日から続く未来は
The future continuing from that day
みんなと誓った今日だよ
Is today, the day I promised to you all
待った 待った 待った 回った
Wait, wait, wait, turning 'round
加速するハート
My heart starts to accelerate
行くよ どこまでも
I'll go anywhere
準備はオッケー?
Are you ready?
開け 夢の扉を
Open the door to your dreams
キラメキライダー!
Kirameki Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキを 響かせよう
Let's make this fresh excitement echo out
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
The best time, with the best friends
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm right here, because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ みんなで歌おう
I came here just to see you, let's all sing together
終わらないメロディ
An endless melody
キラメキにのって
Riding on the sparkle
届いてるかな 私の声
Is my voice reaching you?
届けたいのは 君に笑顔
What I want to give you is a smile
理想と遠すぎて 悔しくて
I felt so far from my ideal, it was frustrating
みんなと泣き笑ったね
We cried and laughed together, didn't we?
ぎゅっと ぎゅっと ぎゅっと ぎゅっと 全て抱きしめて
Holding everything tight, tight, tight
行こう どこまでも 準備はオッケー?
Let's go anywhere, are you ready?
進め 希望の道を
Move forward on the path of hope
キラメキライダー!
Kirameki Rider!
好きな気持ちからふわり 奏でたいな
I want to play a melody from my feelings of love
最高の場所 最高の仲間と
The best place, with the best friends
ここにいるよ 幻なんかじゃない
I'm right here, this isn't an illusion
君の心が幸せに染まるように
So that your heart can be dyed in happiness
重ねてくハーモニー
Layers of harmony
キラメキ纏って
Dressed in sparkle
歌い続けたいな 踊り続けたいな
I want to keep singing, I want to keep dancing
そんな願いは わがままもいいでしょう?
Is it okay to have such selfish wishes?
だって楽しすぎて もう止まらない
Because it's so much fun, I can't stop anymore
輝くステージでもっともっと!
On this shining stage, more and more!
このステージで、この曲を歌えて本当に幸せです!
I'm so happy I could sing this song on this stage!
私もアイドルとして認めてくれますか!?
Will you acknowledge me as an idol too!?
嬉しい 楽しい 愛しい だけじゃ語れない
Happy, fun, beloved—words aren't enough
今も今も 悩みはあるけど
Even now, even now, I still have worries, but
ここにいるよ 私ここにいるよ
I'm right here, I'm right here
君と同じ世界を見つめて
Looking at the same world as you
キラメキライダー!
Kirameki Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキを 響かせよう
Let's make this fresh excitement echo out
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
The best time, with the best friends
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm right here, because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ みんなで歌おう
I came here just to see you, let's all sing together
終わらないメロディ
An endless melody
キラメキにのって
Riding on the sparkle
キラメキ纏って
Dressed in sparkle
今日は、観に来てくれて本当にありがとう♡ 私が「アイドル」なんて... って自分で思っていて自信なかったけど、
Thank you so much for coming to watch today ♡ I used to think 'Me, an idol?' and lacked confidence, but
今なら胸を張っていえるかな!? 何事もあきらめがちだった私がもう一度夢を追いかけたい!! と思えたのは、
maybe now I can say it with pride!? The reason someone like me, who tended to give up on things, felt like wanting to chase a dream one more time!!
ホロライブ、そしてルイ友さんのおかげです!! これからも全力で走り続けるからついて来てね♡
is thanks to Hololive and all the Lui-tomo!! I'll keep running with everything I've got, so please keep following me ♡